[{"question": " hey, remember when i had a monkey?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " yeah, what, what was i thinking?", "answer": "  hey! so, what&#146;s with the 20 percent tip? did i do something wrong?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " twenty percent is a pretty generous tip joe.", "answer": " y&#146;know what&#146;s more generous than that?! fifty percent! y&#146;know what&#146;s even more generous than that?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " i see where you&#146;re goin&#146;!", "answer": " what&#146;s up with the greed joe?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " well isn&#146;t there something you can do to earn a little extra money? i mean, can&#146;t-can&#146;t you pick up, i don&#146;t know, an extra shift here?", "answer": " or, y&#146;know, i used to beg for money. of course it helps if you&#146;ve got y&#146;know a little of this  goin&#146; on. wow! i still have it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " oh, wait! wait! don&#146;t you have an audition today? yeah! maybe you&#146;ll get that job!", "answer": " oh, ha-ha-ha! ooh! wait a minute, i used to get medical experiments down on me all the time!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": "  ah, finally an explanation.", "answer": " no-no! i used to get paid for all kinds of medical stuff, remember? let&#146;s see uh, well i don&#146;t want to donate sperm again.  i really prefer doing that at the home office y&#146;know?  ooh-ooh, maybe they want like some of my blood or-or spit or something, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": "  joey!", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " what did i tell you about talking to your friends while you&#146;re working?", "answer": " uhh do it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " hey, what have you guys been up to?", "answer": " ohh! we went to a self-defense class today!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " wow!", "answer": " yeah, kicking a guy in the crotch all morning really takes it out of ya!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " now, we can kick anybody&#146;s ass!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " after one class? i don&#146;t think so.", "answer": " what? you wanna see me self-defend myself?! go over there  and pretend you&#146;re a sexual predator! go on! i dare ya!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " well, of course you can defend yourself from an attack you know is coming, that&#146;s not enough. look, i studying kara-tay for a long time, and there&#146;s a concept you should really be familiar with. it&#146;s what the japanese call  unagi.", "answer": " isn&#146;t that a kind of sushi?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " no, it&#146;s a concept!", "answer": " yeah it is! it is! it&#146;s freshwater eel!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " all right, maybe it means that too&#133;", "answer": " ohh! i would kill for a salmon skin roll right now!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? fine! get attacked! i don&#146;t even care!", "answer": "  come on ross. we&#146;re sorry. please tell us what it is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " unagi is a state of total awareness. okay? only by achieving true unagi can you be prepared for any danger that may befall you!", "answer": " you mean in case someone is trying to steal your bamboo sleeping mat or your kettle of fish?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": "  ooh! y&#146;know what? if we made reservations, we could have unagi in about a half-hour.", "answer": " y&#146;know what&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " hey-hey, is monica here?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " okay, look i need your help, i don&#146;t know what to get her for valentine&#146;s day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " well, valentine&#146;s day was like two weeks ago, so i wouldn&#146;t get her a calendar!", "answer": "  she was working on valentine&#146;s day so we&#146;re celebrating it tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " ohh, hey! why don&#146;t you book a date for both of you at one of those romantic spas?", "answer": " ooh, joey, that&#146;s actually a really good idea!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " and of course, crotchless panties.", "answer": " well appealing as that does sound to her boyfriend  and her brother,  i can&#146;t do that we promised we&#146;d make each other gifts this year.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " aw, i love that.", "answer": " you guys!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " you can&#146;t make crotchless panties? you take, you take a pair of scissors and you just cut&#133;", "answer": "  okay-okay-okay! so, making things. that sounds like so much fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " yeah, i thought so to until i paper mached one of my eyes shut.", "answer": " oh, i love paper mache! what did you make?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " what is that?", "answer": " nothing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " so what are you gonna do?", "answer": " well, have you guys made anything that maybe i can take credit for?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " ohh! i have! i have! i started making these little sock bunnies!  oh for crying out loud!", "answer": " hey, wait a minute! that is my sock!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey! honey, can i ask you a question about the valentine&#146;s day gifts?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " oh, yeah.", "answer": " do we have to make the entire thing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " yes! why, did you&#151;you forget to make yours?", "answer": " of course, of course not. i just have to uh, go over to the place where i-i made it and pick-pick it up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " okay.  okay, i can&#146;t wait! this is going to be the best valentine&#146;s day ever!  i can&#146;t believe it! make the presents! make the presents!", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": "  hi uh, i&#146;m joey tribbiani and with all do respect i&#146;d like to donate some fluids.", "answer": " we&#146;re actually at the end of one of our research cycles, so we&#146;re not looking for applicants right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " oh that&#146;s too bad. i&#146;ve kinda been saving up.  uh, are you sure there&#146;s no studies i can participate in?", "answer": " well, here&#146;s a schedule of what&#146;s coming up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " oh that one is available now, but only identical twins are eligible. it&#146;s a twins study.", "answer": " but it&#146;s $2,000.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " sorry.", "answer": " well how about this one? testing the effects of joey tribbiani on attractive nurse receptionists.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " ross!!!", "answer": " what the hell was that?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " ohh, you&#146;re a freak!!", "answer": " perhaps. now i&#146;m curious, at what point during those girlish screams would you have begun to kick my ass?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " all right, so we weren&#146;t prepared!", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry i had to take such drastic measures to make my point, but i&#151;look, i just want you guys to be safe.  danger!!!!!  ahhh, huh? unagi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": "  chandler. i sensed it was you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " unagi. i&#146;m always aware.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " okay, are you aware unagi  is an eel?", "answer": " what&#146;s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " i can&#146;t figure out what to make monica.", "answer": " oh, why don&#146;t you make her one of your little jokes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " i&#146;m going crazy! okay? do you have any thing around here that looks homemade?", "answer": " y&#146;know what? she&#146;d-she&#146;d love this.  uh, it&#146;s an exact replica of apollo 8. i made it in the sixth grade.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " yeah, i guess i could use that. i could say that your love sends me to the moon.", "answer": " yeah-yeah, except apollo 8 didn&#146;t actually land on the moon. but you-you-you could write that umm, your love lets me orbit the moon twice and return safely.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " wait a minute, i can&#146;t give this to her.", "answer": " why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " because it says &quot;captain ross&quot; on the side and &quot;i hate monica&quot; on the bottom.", "answer": " oh.  phoebe and rachel: danger!!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " hey! hi! you uh, ready to exchange gifts?", "answer": " sure! okay, you go first.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " okay, come here! come here.", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " now, it&#146;s not wrapped because i just, just finished it.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " but i made you a tape of what i think are all romantic songs.", "answer": " oh, what a great gift! is the way you look tonight on it?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  maybe we&#146;ll have to listen and see!", "answer": " oh, i love it! thank you so much!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " okay, you ready to open yours?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " it&#146;s a sock bunny.", "answer": " yeah-yeah, you remember how i call you bunny?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " not really.", "answer": " well, i did one time, and-and i want to start doing it more. see that&#146;s what this is about.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " i see. y&#146;know umm, phoebe makes sock bunnies.", "answer": " no! no, she doesn&#146;t. uh phoebe, what she makes&#151;that&#146;s uh&#151;they&#146;re sock rabbits. they are completely different&#151;okay! okay! okay! i didn&#146;t make it! i&#146;m sorry! i totally forgot about tonight and the fact that we&#146;re supposed to make the presents!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " oh, it&#146;s okay. i don&#146;t&#133;", "answer": " no-no, it&#146;s not okay! it&#146;s not! i mean you were just&#133; you&#146;re so incredible! you went through all this time and effort to make this tape for me! y&#146;know i&#146;m just gonna&#151;i, i am gonna make this up to you! i will! i-i am going to cook anything you want in here , and i am going to do anything you want in there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " wow!  you are way to young to have seen that!", "answer": " oops!  y&#146;know, your birthday is in a month-and-a-half, what do you say i forget to get you a present for that too?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " you are totally and completely 100% forgiven.", "answer": " we have got to wash that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " do you remember that jacket that you love so much, that you thought was too expensive?", "answer": " you have done enough!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " i wanna wake up early and go get it for you!", "answer": " no you don&#146;t&#151;get it in black, not brown.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " oop, your cake is ready!", "answer": " oop!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " who the hell are you?!", "answer": " i&#146;m joey! how are you doin&#146;?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " look, i got to apologize on the behalf of carl.", "answer": " who the hell is carl?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " oh, did i not mention? carl is a guy i hired to be my identical twin for a medical research project.", "answer": " y&#146;know sometimes the good ideas are just right in front of you, aren&#146;t they?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " the only problem!", "answer": " yeah, he&#146;s the reason i didn&#146;t get that big minute maid commercial a couple of years ago remember? we were supposed to be brothers, but he messed it up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": "  hey, uh can i get a little piece of that cake?", "answer": "  pizza!! we like pizza!! get out!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " pat sajak?", "answer": " yep!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " alex trebek?", "answer": " oh, of course!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " chuck woolery?", "answer": " definitely! phoebe, you will not find a single game show host, who&#146;s ass i cannot kick.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " say it!", "answer": " say we are unagi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " it&#146;s not something you are! it&#146;s something you have!", "answer": " say it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " all right carl, we&#146;re next. now remember, what is not gonna be?", "answer": " another minute maid fiasco.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " that&#146;s right! and what are you not gonna do?", "answer": " well, i&#146;m not gonna talk because&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " that&#146;s us.", "answer": "  but uh, this is a study for identical twins.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " that&#146;s right, $2,000.", "answer": " but, you&#146;re not identical twins.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " oh my good god.", "answer": " hey! continuing the countdown of your favorite meals. tonight, no. 3, macaroni and cheese with cut up hot dogs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " look, you have done enough! okay? you have to stop this now.", "answer": " i will! but not tonight. for dinner music, i thought we could listen to that tape you made me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " i love the way you look every night chandler!  that&#146;s why i made you this tape! happy birthday! love janice!", "answer": " no! you&#146;re the sweetest!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " it&#146;s a great class.", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " yeah, yeah, i was watching.  umm, hey, a couple of questions though. umm, about that-that-that last move where the woman tripped you and then pinned you to the floor, what-what-what-what would you do next?", "answer": " well, she would take her keys and try to jam them&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " no. no-no. no. what would you do next?", "answer": " who? me the attacker?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " yes that&#146;s right.", "answer": " why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " i tired attacking two women, did not work.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " no, i mean it&#146;s okay, i mean, they&#146;re-they&#146;re my friends. in fact, i-i-i was married to one of them.", "answer": " let me get this straight man, you attacked your ex-wife?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " i am so, so, so, so sorry!", "answer": "  uh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": "  yeah you will!  and, are you kiddin&#146; me?!", "answer": " come on monica, it&#146;s our valentine&#146;s day. please? please-please, please?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " so, are we going in there?", "answer": " i am!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " why is ross doing that?", "answer": " danger!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " oh my god! why is he jumping on those women!", "answer": " we should help him!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep17.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}]